(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-12T22:25:42.870107",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
【注意事項】照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OK
[Notice] Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK
【ご来場のお客様へ】照明の点滅にご注意ください／声出し応援OKです
[Notice to Visitors] Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is OK!
だ・か・ら 君のことだいすき だいすき だいすき だいすき だ・い・す・き
So... I love you, love you, love you, love you, I love you!
溢れるこの愛は きっとずっと もう止まらない
This overflowing love will surely never stop!
あいあい あいあい ♡ あいらぶゆー
Aiai aiai ♡ I love you
君が あいあい あいあい ♡ あいにじゅー
You, aiai aiai ♡ I need you
好きだけ愛してね
Just love me as much as you like
揺れるハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My swaying heart goes bounce, bounce, bounce
穴に落ちてあびゃびゃ
Falling into a hole, abyabya!
こんなになってもまだ抜け出せない
Even like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかねぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui, nui, nui!
助けて君たち アホイホイ
Save me, everyone! Ahoy-hoy!
もっと もっと
More! More!
好きだけ愛してね
Just love me as much as you like
アニメにハマって
Got super into anime,
歌いたくなっちゃった！
and really felt like singing!
推しのシーン見ながら
Singing karaoke...
カラオケ歌えるなんて...
while watching scenes of my fave...
尊すぎてツラいっ！
is so precious it hurts!
歌いたいアニソン・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Find anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND
吉野家で
At Yoshinoya,
ごはんしょ♪
let's eat!
ぎゅう
Beef...
ぎゅう ぎゅう
beef, beef...
ぎゅう
Beef...
うまっ！
Delicious!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Taste the original's passion.
牛丼は吉野家
Gyudon is Yoshinoya.
やっぱこれだな！
Gotta be this!
せーの！
Ready, set...
本日は
Today,
ホロライブ 3rd Generation Live
hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦
Operation Kyururun:
最強アイドル、推すしか無いでしょ！に
Ultimate Idols: You Have To Support Us!
ご来場いただき
thank you for coming to...
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内をさせていただきます
To ensure everyone enjoys the live concert until the end, here are a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします
The use of photography, audio, or video recording equipment during the show is strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください
If you happen to feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform nearby staff.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他の皆の迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です
Actions inside the venue like moshing, diving, or throwing items onto the stage that cause trouble or disrupt the show are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and enjoy the show!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります
Also, video streaming and photography cameras are in the venue, so audience seats may be captured on camera.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能が... 可能性がありまーすので！
These videos and photos may be used... may be used for promotional purposes, so...
あらかじめご了承ください
Please be aware of this in advance.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは #きゅるるん大作戦DAY1 です
Also, the concert hashtag is #KyururunDaisakusenDAY1.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです！
We'd love it if you use the hashtag to hype things up!
それでは開演までもうしばらくです
Now then, there is just a little time left until opening.
みんなの声をたくさん聞かせてぺこ！
Let me hear lots of your voices, peko!
それじゃあ3期生、円陣行くかー！
Alright, 3rd Generation, let's do our huddle!
みんな今からマイクが無くなるので、静かに！静かに！
Everyone, the mics will be off now, so be quiet! Quiet!
アイアイアイアイ LOVE YOU もう アイアイアイアイ NEED YOU
I-I-I-I love you! More! I-I-I-I need you!
もっと もっと もっと もっと 好きなだけ愛させて！
More, more, more, more! Let me love you as much as I want!
3期生ライブいくぺこー！
3rd Generation Live, here we go, peko!
みんなで最高の思い出作ろうね！
Let's create the best memories together with everyone!
メロメロのナイツ 君だらけ 溶かしてるわねわたし
Head-over-heels nights, filled with you, you're melting me...
心臓ドキドキになっている警報
My heart is beating so fast—it's an alarm!
毎日幻覚現れて
Daily hallucinations appearing,
頭に花咲いちゃって
flowers blooming in my head...
恋ってやつは非常識ですわ
This thing called love is truly irrational!
いっそ食べちゃいたい フリーズした感情
I want to eat you up—my frozen feelings,
誰もが思ってる お願い
everyone feels it too, please!
チュンチュンチュン 萌え化 どんどんして急上昇
Chun-chun-chun, getting so cute! Surging rapidly!
これが恋ならもう後悔しないわ
If this is love, I won't regret it anymore!
だーからー 君のこと 大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き！
That's why... I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!
あふれるこの愛は きっとずっと止まらない！
This overflowing love surely won't stop, forever!
アイアイアイアイ LOVE YOU 君が アイアイアイアイ NEED YOU
I-I-I-I love you! You are... I-I-I-I need you!
もっと もっと もっと もっと 好きなだけ愛させて！
More, more, more, more! Let me love you as much as I want!
ゆるゆるハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My relaxed heart goes bounce-bounce-bounce,
罠に落ちてあわわ
falling into a trap, oh my!
こんなになっても今更抜け出せない
Even if I end up like this, I can't escape now!
どうしたもんかねぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nui-nui-nui?
助けて君旅 Ahoy hoy
Save me on your journey, Ahoy hoy!
もっと もっと もっと もっと 好きなだけ愛してね！
More, more, more, more! Love me as much as you want!
ふわふわ浮かぶ夢の中
Floating softly in a dream,
君の声で目が覚めた
I was awakened by your voice.
五感全部が君一色になる
All five senses become colored solely by you.
毎度お騒がせごめん
Sorry for causing trouble every time,
キュンで壊れちゃいそうだ
I feel like breaking from heartbeats!
恋ってやつは制御不能ですわ
This thing called love is uncontrollable!
いっそ抱きしめて 壊してもいいよ
Just hold me tight, you can break me if you want,
誰にも邪魔はさせない
I won't let anyone get in the way!
ピチピチ感情で
With fresh, lively feelings,
ギラギラ急展開
a sparkling, rapid plot twist!
これが運命ならもう迷わない
If this is destiny, I won't hesitate anymore!
覚悟してね！ 君だけが 大好き大好き大好き大好き大スキ！
Prepare yourself! It's only you that I love, love, love, love, love so much!
私のこの愛は ずっとずっと離さない！
This love of mine, I'll never ever let it go!
Be Be Be my baby 愛の Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss to me!
Be-be-be my baby! Give your love kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss to me!
もっと もっと もっと もっと 私だけを見ててね！
More, more, more, more! Keep looking only at me!
無視したら泣いちゃうかもね
If you ignore me, I might cry...
だってそんなの聞いてない ぺこちゃん
'Cause Pekora never heard about that!
わかってるよねダリン 大愛をまっすぐ
You understand, right, darling? Sending big love straight to you!
ノエル！ ぺこら！ フレア！ マリン！ もっと！
Noel! Pekora! Flare! Marine! More!
ホロライブファンタジーを 愛してるー！
We love Hololive Fantasy!
君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れるこの愛は ずっとずっと止まらない
This overflowing love will never, ever stop!
I I I I I love you 君が
I, I, I, I, I love you! You are...
I I I I I need you
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more!
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want!
ときめくハートが ぴょんぴょんぴょん
My fluttering heart goes hop, hop, hop!
矢に射抜かれて あわわわ
Pierced by an arrow, flustered and wild!
こんなになったら 魔法は解けません
Once it gets like this, the magic won't break!
本気になってる ぬいぬいぬい
Getting totally serious, Nui-Nui-Nui!
行ってきますまで あほいほい
Until "I'm off!", Ahoy-Ahoy!
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more!
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want!
I I I I I love you
I I I I I need you
私たちの愛をもっと！
Take more of our love!
叫べ愛のコール！
[Shout your call of love!]
あんちゃん ぴちぴち (Ahoy!)
An-chan is fresh and young! (Ahoy!)
ピチピチ (Ahoy!)
Fresh and young! (Ahoy!)
色気担当の マリンです
I'm Marine, in charge of sex appeal!
キャプテン！
Captain!
踊る Ahoy に 見る Ahoy
Ahoy if you dance, Ahoy if you watch!
たまに脱ぐらくんに くまもりましゅぶこ
Sometimes stripping down into a swimsuit!
おーマリン！ マリン船長だろ！
Oh, Marine! Captain Marine, right?!
うさぎ 透明
Rabbit, transparent,
最強 女神 ぺこら
Strongest goddess, Pekora!
ぺこら！ ママ！ よしよししてー！
Pekora! Mommy! Pat my head!
ちょっと 横取りめ 横取りかー！
Hey, wait! Stealing the spotlight?!
ぺこぺこ うさぎか？ 大成功の ため！
Peko-peko rabbit? For super success!
条件 コールも
Even conditional calls,
いけちゃう？
Can we do it?
きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん アイドル
Kyurun, kyurun, kyurun, kyurun idol!
実家のような 安心コールー
A comforting chant like being home!
お決まりの ファンサービス
The usual fan service,
あふれちゃう！
Overflowing!
きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん アイドル
Kyurun, kyurun, kyurun, kyurun idol!
極めた ヲタ芸 踊るー
Dancing master-level Wota-gei!
新規もいる 古参いる
Newbies are here, veterans are here,
もはや 生きがいなのかな？ ってじゃん！
Isn't this already our reason for living?!
会いたい！ 推したい！
Want to meet! Want to support!
おきまりコールで！
With the usual chant!
現場で テンプレ 応援 キュルキュル
Template cheering at the venue, kyuru-kyuru!
チアー！ チアー！
Cheer! Cheer!
フレ！ フレ！ エルフ フレア！
Hooray! Hooray! Elf Flare!
褒められて 照れるでぃす
Getting praised and getting shy!
はいはい！ 世界で一番
Yeah, yeah! The most in the world,
愛してる！
I love you!
チャンネル登録 なんと無料！
Subscribing to the channel is totally free!
Joy Joy! Enjoy! 団長のノエル
Joy, joy! Enjoy! Knight Commander Noel!
ふわふわ のーきん 女騎士だよ
Fluffy muscle-brained female knight!
筋肉みたい？ ぎゅー！
Want to see muscles? Squeeze!
ぎゅー！ ギュッ！
Squeeze! Tight!
タイムに！
Time to!
感謝より 愛込めて！
Put in love rather than just thanks!
俺たち 実質 メンバー！
We're practically members!
きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん アイドル
Kyurun, kyurun, kyurun, kyurun idol!
ハートマーク 振り付けも コピるー
Copying the heart mark dance moves!
可愛いとか 声でつき こじらせちゃう！
Cute voice driving everyone crazy!
きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん アイドル
Kyurun, kyurun, kyurun, kyurun idol!
概念カラーも 集める
Gathering concept colors!
ガチ勢も エル勢も
Hardcore fans, light fans,
もはや 全員 愛おし 決定じゃん！
Every single one of you is adorable, that's settled!
生きたい！ ノリたい！
Want to live! Want to groove!
現場で 全力 応援 キュルキュル
Giving full-power support at the venue, kyuru-kyuru!
チアー！ チアー！
Cheer! Cheer!
みんなの 王様！
Everyone's king!
みんなの 歌姫！
Everyone's songstress!
みんなの 団長！
Everyone's commander!
みんなの 船長！
Everyone's captain!
LOVE&PEACE な時も
In times of love and peace,
推しがへこんだ 時でも
Even when your fave feels down,
トライ＆エラー 重ねたい
Want to try and err together,
君と見たい 景色があるんだ！
There's a scenery I want to see with you!
きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん アイドル
Kyurun, kyurun, kyurun, kyurun idol!
実家のような 安心コールー
A comforting chant like being home!
お決まりの ファンサービス 大好き！ 一生好きだよー！
The usual fan service, love it! Love you forever!
きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん アイドル
Kyurun, kyurun, kyurun, kyurun idol!
ラストまで 追いかけるー
Chasing till the very end!
年賀状 届く方？
Anyone getting New Year's cards?
存在が 最強 最優勝！
Your existence is the strongest, ultimate victory!
きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん きゅるん アイドル
Kyurun, kyurun, kyurun, kyurun idol!
永遠の愛 誓えるー
Can vow eternal love!
尊いー！ 尊いー！
Precious! Precious!
尊いー！ もはや 生涯オタク 決定じゃん！
Precious! Isn't being an otaku for life already settled?!
それなー！
Totally!
もうずっと... もうずっと...
Forever and ever... Forever and ever...
現場で 限界応援！ キュルキュル！
Cheering to our limits at the venue! Kyuru-kyuru!
ちあ！ちあ！
Cheer! Cheer!
一生懸命で ちあ！
Do your absolute best, cheer!
ちょっとテンション上がりすぎた！
We got a bit too excited!
落ち着いて！
Calm down!
落ち着いたところで自己紹介を開始しようということで
Now that we've calmed down, let's start with our introductions!
自己紹介ね！
Introductions, right!
じゃあ、ぺこらからいきますよ！
Alright, Pekora will go first!
こんぺこ こんぺこ こんぺこ！
Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko!
ホロライブ3期生の兎田ぺこらっと...
I'm Usada Pekora of Hololive 3rd Generation...
ちょっと！言わせてあげようよ！みんな言いたいんだから！
Wait! Let them say it too! Everyone wants to say it!
もう1回やってよ！
Do it one more time!
何て言えばいいの？
What should we say?
こんぺこ こんぺこ こんぺこって言ったら、向こうも言いたいんだよ！
When I say "Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko," they want to respond!
あ、そういうことね！
Ah, I see!
言ってくれますかー？
Will you say it with me?
じゃあ行きますよ！
Alright, here we go!
こんぺこ こんぺこ こんぺこ！
Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko!
いいー！
Nice!
ホロライブ3期生の兎田ぺこらっと...
I'm Usada Pekora of Hololive 3rd Generation...
はい、じゃあフレアは「こんぬい」じゃなくて「ハイダーリン」って言うから
Okay, so Flare, instead of "Konnui", she'll say "Hi Darlin'"...
「ハイハニー」って返してください！
So please reply with "Hi Honey"!
ハイダーリン！
Hi Darlin'!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生の不知火フレアと...
I'm Shiranui Flare of Hololive 3rd Generation, and...
はい、じゃあ団長は「牛丼は？」って言うんで「並盛！」って言ってください！
Okay! Next, as for Dancho, I'll ask, "How do you like your beef bowl?" So please say, "Regular size!"
じゃあ行くよ！牛丼はー？
Alright, here we go! How do you like your beef bowl?
イェーイ！そうよね！
Yay! That's right!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと...
I'm Shirogane Noel of Hololive 3rd Generation, and...
キミたち... 今もしかして、フレアのこと「ハニー」って言った？
You guys... Did you just call Flare "Honey"?
言ってない！お前だよ！
We didn't! She meant you!
団長のこと忘れて言ってみたの？
Did you say it while forgetting about Dancho?
なんちゃって！
Just kidding!
じゃあ普通に「Ahoy!」で行きますんで、「Ahoy!」って言ってくださいね！
Okay then, let me do the usual "Ahoy!", so please say "Ahoy!" back, okay?
あほーい！
Ahoy!
誰があほや！
Who are you calling a fool?!
なんちゃって！
Just kidding!
ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンでーす！
Hololive 3rd Generation, Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine here!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
なんかさ、みんなアイドル口上みたいなのさ、ブログに書いたやつやる？
Hey, should we do those idol intro chants that we posted on the blog?
やろうよ！やるしかないよね！
Let's do it! We gotta do it!
じゃあ配信でね、また順番で行きましょう！
Let's go in order then!
みんな覚えてるよね？ぺこらの口上！
Everyone remembers Pekora's chant, right?
絶対覚えてねぇぞ...
I bet nobody remembers...
覚えている人、手挙げて！
Raise your hands if you remember!
あ！手上がってる！
Ah! Hands are raised!
全然覚えてないや！全然覚えてねぇって！
They don't remember at all! Nobody knows it at all!
じゃあ今から覚えてくださいね！じゃあぺこらからいきますよ！
Well, learn it starting now! Alright, Pekora will start!
ラビット！キャロット！キラッと登場！
Rabbit! Carrot! Making a sparkling appearance!
最強アイドルぺこらが来たぺこ！
The strongest idol, Pekora, has arrived-peko!
まだまだ続くよ！ぺこらんストーリー！
It's just getting started, Pekoran Story!
見て！キラキラしてるー！
Look! It's so sparkly!
フレア、めっちゃ難しいんだけどさ、いけるかな？
Flare's is super difficult, but can you do it?
いけるいける！
We can do it!
みんなにもコール＆レスポンスして欲しくて、「準備は？」って言ったら「バンタン！」
I want everyone to do a call-and-response. When I ask "Ready?", say "All set!"
「コールは？」って聞くので「カンタン！」って言ってください！
When I ask "The call?", please say "Easy!"
手拍子「パン！パン！パン！」
Clap three times! "Clap! Clap! Clap!"
「ステップ？」「ガンガン！」
"Steps?" "Go hard!"
「私は？」「ふーたん！」
"And I am?" "Fuutan!"
めっちゃ難しいやん！これ練習ね！覚えてください！
That's super difficult! That was practice! Please remember it!
では行きますよ！こんぬい！「準備はー？」
Okay, here we go! Konnui! "Ready?"
「コールはー？」
"The call?"
手拍子！
Clapping!
「ステップー？」
"Steps?"
「私はー？」
"And I am?"
ホロライブ3期生不知火フレアです！
I'm Shiranui Flare of Hololive 3rd Generation!
おー！すごい！
Woah! Amazing!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
難しいのにすごいですよ！
That was hard, but you guys were amazing!
次はノエル！
Next is Noel!
ノエル行きます！団長コール＆レスポンスないから、ちょっとラップします！
Noel's turn! Dancho doesn't have a call-and-response, so I'll do a rap!
こっから行こうかな！
From here... shall we go!
ねぇ何にしよ？
Hey, what should I choose?
注文至高の食べ物
Ordering the supreme food,
答えは牛丼
the answer is beef bowl!
大盛りで飲み物
Large serving is a drink,
みんなの胸に急行
express train to everyone's hearts!
ダメダメ重工
No-no heavy industry,
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエル！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel!
マリン、まあ恒例なんですけど、先に予習しましょうか。
Well, as is tradition, shall we practice first?
マリンが「マリンは」って言ったら、返しは「船長！」で。
When I say "Marine is...", you respond with "Captain!"
マリン「船長！」で。
I'll say Marine, you say "Captain!"
「君たちは？」「一味！」
"And you are?" "Ichimi!"
「我ら無敵の」「海賊団！」
"Our invincible..." "Pirate crew!"
で、最後に「宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです」って言うから、そしたら問答無用で「カワイイ！」って言う。
And at the end, I'll say "Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine here!", so then without question, you say "Cute!"
分かりましたね？
Got it?
まぁ余裕だよね。
Well, that should be easy.
ナイス、素晴らしい返事できて、丸！じゃあ行きますよ！
Nice, wonderful response! Passed! Okay, here we go!
マリンはー？ / 船長！
Marine is...? / Captain!
君たちはー？ / 一味！
And you are...? / Ichimi!
我ら無敵のー？ / 海賊団！
Our invincible...? / Pirate crew!
宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです！
Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine here!
カワイイー！
Cute!
いやー気持ちいいー、これ！
Man, that feels so good!
よかったなー「カワイイ」って言われて！よかったなー！
Glad you got called "cute"! Good for you!
そんなことないけど... / カワイイ！
Well, it's nothing much... / Cute!
え、でもコールアンドレスポンスね、ちょっと1発目からもうすごい難しいのやらせちゃってどうもすみませんね。
Wait, but sorry for making you do such a difficult call-and-response right off the bat.
ねー、たくさんちょっと... ありがとう！
Yeah, thanks a lot!
声が聞こえますよ！
We can hear your voices!
さっきのさー、うちらのエンジン聞こえました？
Could you hear our huddle sound earlier?
聞こえた！聞こえた！
We heard it! We heard it!
ちょっとね、聞こえるかなーって不安だったの。
I was a bit worried if you could hear it or not.
こっちにはね、君らの声よく聞こえるんだけどさ、さすがにマイク介さないとちっちゃかったかなーと思って。
We can hear your voices really well from here, but I thought maybe it'd be too quiet without a mic.
いや、お腹から出してお腹から！ねー。
No, we shouted from our stomachs! Right?
聞こえたー！
We heard it!
聞こえるよー！こっちにも声聞こえてますよ！
We can hear you! We hear your voices over here too!
衣装のことも言わなきゃ！
We gotta talk about the outfits too!
そうだよ！
That's right!
突然の新衣装！
Surprise new outfits!
カワイイでしょ？
Aren't they cute?
ちょっとずつ違うところがありますんで。
There are subtle differences for each of us.
ペコラは、みみー！
Pekora has ear...
輪っかがついているぺこー！
It has a halo on it, peko!
なんと考案者はノエちゃん！
And the one who came up with it was Noel-chan!
そう！ノエル！すごいでしょう？
Yep! Noel! Isn't that awesome?
マリンはね、ヘッドドレスがね、ほら、こんな感じで、バツバツバツバツ！
For Marine, the head dress is like this, with X's everywhere!
カワイイー！
Cute!
団長なんかポンポンついてまーす！
Dancho has pom-poms on hers!
フレアは、この頭のリボンかな？
For Flare, maybe the ribbon on her head?
カワイイね！靴下も違いますね！
So cute! The socks are different too!
フレアはギャルじゃないんでね。
Flare isn't a gal.
私もギャル！ペコラもギャル！
I'm a gal! Pekora is a gal too!
ギャルです！
I'm a gal!
あの、うちらね、めっちゃ喋りすぎてるみたいで...
Um, it seems like we've been talking way too much...
嘘でしょ！
No way!
このまま音楽しないのかい、みたいな。
Like, "are they even gonna play music?" kind of thing.
スタッフさんに注意されましたけれど...
The staff warned us, but...
ちなみに、配信で見ている方、YouTubeで見ている方、概要欄にね、配信チケットのリンクがありますので、ぜひ！
By the way, for those watching the stream on YouTube, there's a link for stream tickets in the description box, so please check it out!
次の曲でちょっとチラ見せは終わっちゃうので、今のうちに！
The sneak peek will end with the next song, so do it while you still can!
見てほしいパートがいっぱいあるんで！
There are so many parts we want you to see!
お願いします！
Please check it out!
「#3期生テルル大作戦DAY1」でいっぱい呟いてねー！
Tweet lots with "#3期生テルル大作戦DAY1"!
つぶやいてくださーい！
Please tweet it!
ていうか、そうだ、これもやらないと！
Wait, that's right, we have to do this too!
あのね、生バンドがね、すごいカッコいいじゃない？
You know, the live band is super cool, right?
だからちょっと聞かせたくて。じゃあペコラちゃんから言ってもらっていいですか？
So I want you to hear them. Okay, Pekora-chan, could you go first?
了解！エアバンド、キーボード担当、兎田ペコラー！
Roger! Air band keyboardist, Usada Pekora!
すげー！めちゃ弾いてる！
Awesome! They're playing so well!
よし、行くよ！ギター、宝鐘マリン！
Alright, here we go! Guitar, Houshou Marine!
おー！カッコいい！
Woah! So cool!
はい、ドラム、白銀ノエル！
Alright, drums, Shirogane Noel!
ドドドドドド！
Dodododododo!
すごーい！やばい！カッコよ！
Awesome! Amazing! So cool!
じゃあフレア、ベースやります！
Okay, Flare will do the bass!
おー！カッコいい！
Woah! So cool!
あーカッコいいわ！最高！
Ah, so cool! The best!
はい、うちらが演奏してまーす！演奏してるやーん！
Yes, we're the ones playing! We're totally playing!
あ、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょうか！
Ah, shall we move on to the next song soon?
場所！場所！あ、こっちか！あ、ここね！
Positions! Positions! Ah, over here! Ah, right here!
はい、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょう！せーの！
Okay, let's move on to the next song! Ready, set...
リアリティ・ファンタジー！
Reality Fantasy!
H-O-L-O-L-I-V-E F-A-N-T-A-S-Y
冒険 出発 さあ
Adventure, departure, come on!
挑戦 開始 さあ
Challenge, start, come on!
冒険 出発 さあ
Adventure, departure, come on!
挑戦 開始 さあ
Challenge, start, come on!
冒険 出発 さあ
Adventure, departure, come on!
挑戦 開始 さあ
Challenge, start, come on!
冒険 出発 さあ
Adventure, departure, come on!
挑戦 開始 さあ
Challenge, start, come on!
お宝探しに 大海原へ出航だ
Setting sail into the vast ocean to search for treasure!
さあ！
Now!
挑戦！
The challenge...
開始！
...begins!
さあ！
Come on!
耳も心もぴょんぴょん ワワク ちょっぴり ちょっぴり
Ears and hearts hopping, fluttering with excitement, just a bit!
冒険！
Adventure!
出発！
Set sail!
さあ！
Come on!
挑戦！
The challenge...
開始！
...begins!
さあ！
Now!
水平線 向こうから
From beyond the horizon,
新天地 待っててね
wait for us in this brave new world!
運命なんか 飛び越して
We'll leap right over destiny...
その先へ さあ
...and go beyond! Come on!
リアリティ ファンタジー 2つの狭間で
Right between reality and fantasy,
夢歌え 声高く 一緒に さあ
sing of your dreams at the top of your voice together! Come on!
まだ見ない 世界へと 君を連れてくよ
We'll take you to an unseen world!
みんなが繋がる 物語
A story connecting us all...
さあ 始まるよ
...is about to begin!
冒険！
Adventure!
出発！
Set sail!
さあ！
Come on!
挑戦！
The challenge...
開始！
...begins!
さあ！
Now!
冒険！
Adventure!
出発！
Set sail!
さあ！
Come on!
挑戦！
The challenge...
開始！
...begins!
さあ！
Now!
みんなの志 抱き
Carrying everyone's aspirations,
いざ行こう 騎士団集合！
off we go! Knights, assemble!
冒険！
Adventure!
出発！
Set sail!
さあ！
Come on!
挑戦！
The challenge...
開始！
...begins!
さあ！
Now!
胸に宿る太陽 風を切って
With the sun dwelling in our hearts, cutting through the wind,
さらに輝け！
shine even brighter!
冒険！
Adventure!
出発！
Set sail!
さあ！
Come on!
挑戦！
The challenge...
開始！
...begins!
さあ！
Now!
名誉と夢 晴天に掲げたら
Once we raise our honor and dreams under clear skies,
突撃だー！
charge forward!
妖精たち この旅 見守って
Fairies, watch over us on this journey!
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー 2つの狭目で
Right between reality and fantasy,
帆を上げて 迎え ユートピアへ
raise the sails and head towards Utopia!
さあ それぞれの世界から 垣根を越えたら
Once we cross the barriers from our respective worlds,
みんなが繋がる 物語
a story connecting us all...
さあ 始まるよ
...is about to begin!
明るく陽気に 荒波乗り越え
Brightly and cheerfully overcoming the rough waves,
ホロライブ！
hololive!
愛嬌開放 うさ耳すまして
Releasing charm, perking up bunny ears,
ホロライブ！
hololive!
騎士道と誇り 胸に刻むなら
Engraving knighthood and pride into your chest,
ホロライブ！
hololive!
神話に伝わる 神秘な囁き
A mythical whisper passed down in legend,
ホロライブ！
hololive!
冒険！
Adventure!
出発！
Set sail!
さあ！
Come on!
挑戦！
The challenge...
開始！
...begins!
さあ！
Now!
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー 2つの狭間で
Right between reality and fantasy,
夢歌え 声高く 一緒に
sing of your dreams at the top of your voice together!
さあ まだ見ない 世界へと
Come on, to an unseen world...
君を連れてくよ
...we'll take you along!
準備はほら 出来たよ
Look, we're all ready!
ルートもさあ 決まったよ
The route has been set!
みんなが繋がる 物語
A story connecting us all...
さあ 始まるよ
...is about to begin!
時は2026年！
The year is 2026!
2回目の3期生ライブ！
The second 3rd Gen Live!
このチャンスを逃してなるものか！
I won't let this opportunity slip by!
今こそ、全人類ウサギ化計画を...
Now is the time to...
遂行するぺこ！
...execute the All-Humanity Rabbitification Plan, peko!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!]
The free portion has ended. Thank you for watching!